<?xml version="1.0"?>
<req id="SP_HT_62" company="Andrews Federal Credit Union" title="Teller (cash handling exp)">
  <url>https://tekapplicant.tekgriller.com/jobs/reqdetail.asp?reqid=6390</url>
  <city>Suitland</city>
  <state>MD</state>
  <zip>20746</zip>
  <job>Teller</job>
  <type>Part-time</type>
  <description>
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;		Tellers are the face of the company interacting in-person with our customers on a daily basis, providing the highest level of customer service. In this role once up to speed, you will be servicing the customer and be responsible for processing transactions accurately in a timely manner, in accordance with the company's guidelines, as well as handling general enquiries from the customers.  If you enjoy this kind of daily interaction with people, then this may be the job for you. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;		&lt;strong&gt; JOB RESPONSIBILITIES: &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;		- Handling customers with banking related issues, complaints or general enquiries
&lt;br /&gt;		- Accurately maintain your cash drawer throughout your shift
&lt;br /&gt;		- Deposit funds into the customer's accounts and withdraw cash as necessary 
&lt;br /&gt;		- Be proactive and aware of customers in line as well as being ready to assist other tellers 
&lt;br /&gt;		- Willingness to cross-sell other products and services to the customer, or else be prepared to generate additional leads for our sales team to close
&lt;br /&gt;		- Be trained on the company's procedures, policies, processes and software systems after orientation and training
&lt;br /&gt;		
&lt;br /&gt;		&lt;strong&gt; JOB REQUIREMENTS: &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;		- Comfortable learning and using banking software system
&lt;br /&gt;		- At least 12 months interacting with customers on a daily work basis
&lt;br /&gt;		- Previous Teller experience a plus
&lt;br /&gt;		- Use of 10-key adding machine desirable
&lt;br /&gt;		- Good basic math skills
&lt;br /&gt;		- Good listening and communication skills
&lt;br /&gt;		- High school diploma or equivalent
&lt;br /&gt;		- Fluency speaking other languages fluently in addition to English a plus
&lt;br /&gt;		- Willing to work flexible schedules that include weekends and holidays
&lt;br /&gt;		- Ability to stand for extended periods of time
	
&lt;p&gt;		This job description is intended to be a generic description of the  responsibilities and qualifications needed to perform this job, and is therefore not intended to be all inclusive.&lt;/p&gt;
		
&lt;p&gt;		Andrews Federal Credit Union is an equal opportunity employer. No employee or applicant for employment will be discriminated against because of race, color, religion, national origin, physical or mental disability, age, gender, sexual orientation, veteran's status, or status as a disabled veteran or veteran of the Vietnam era.&lt;/p&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt; 		To apply for this position, please copy and paste the following link into your browser address bar:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
  </description>
</req>